(Howard:)You can't develop
a problem that fast.
(Sheldon:)You want to bet?
Oh, great,
(Sheldon:)now I'm addicted to gambling.
(Leonard:)We can't afford to lose
any more time.
(Howard:)Well, this probably won't
work, but has anyone ever tried
(Howard:)to just haul off and
whoop the crazy out of him?
(Leonard:)That's not helpful.
(Leonard:)It's fun to think about,
but it's not helpful.
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon, we are on
a serious time crunch.
(Leonard:)We can't do this
without you.
(Leonard:)Can you please
pull it together?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
Yes, of course.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Just, please, bear with me
if I display symptoms
(Sheldon:)of caffeine withdrawal.
(Howard:)No worries.